

4159871610 sherrydu9@gmail.com sherrydu.net

PRO SKILLS

Sketch App
Principle for Mac
Adobe Illustrator
Adobe Photshop
Adobe After Effect
Adobe Indesign
SketchUp (Architecture)
CAD

Lumion 2020 Chief Are

Chief Architect

HTML CSS

EDUCATION

MA Degree Web Design & New

Media

Academy of Art University

Jun 2018 - Dec 2019 San Francisco

MA Degree Landscape Architecture Academy of Art University

Jan 2014 - May 2016 San Francisco

BA Degree

Environmental Art

Design

Xian Academy of Fine

Art University

Sep 2009 - Jul 2013

Sherry Du

Prodyct Designer

SUMMARY

I am a designer with mixed experience in graphic, print, web, branding and presentation design based in sunny San Francisco, CA. I consider myself not only as a designer but a creative thinker, researcher, and collaborator. I hope my design can help shape the world to better fulfill people's needs and show everyone the beauty of life.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Visual Designer

CTC Food International

Jun 2019 - Present / Richmond, US

I am working at CTC Food International where I am responsible for the e-commerce site, which designs website and implements it from our system. I am working with development team to update our website. In addition, produce on-brand visual assets for marketing, social media, business collaterals, and packaging design.

Graphic Designer

Teance Fine Teas

Feb 2019 - May 2019 / Berkeley, US

I was a graphic designer at Teance where I was responsible for rebranding and new marketing initiatives. In addition, I was also responsible for the e-commerce site, which for the rebranding included an overhaul for layout and branding guidelines.

Interior Design Assistant

CBW Construction

Jan 2017 - Feb 2018 / South San Francisco, US

Working as a designer assistant in an architecture company to draft 3D interior drafting for projects in San Francisco. Working on kitchen cabinet design and drawing in a brand of the company.

Art consultant & teacher

Three Cats Art Institution

Oct 2018 / Lanzhou, China

Working as an art consultant in an art institution to develop a clear understanding of the client's art needs and interests. I also work some personal courses for individuals who want to get in the art field.

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Lead designer for graphic

Blockchain Economic Forum

Jul 2018 / San Francisco

As a graphic designer in the item, our project called KryptoKeds that awarded the running up of "companies" at the BEF.

India basin Park Project Design

Academy of Art Spring Show

Jun 2016 / San Francisco

The project "India Basin Park" was showed at the Academy of Art University, Spring Show.